http://www.iroquoismemorial.com/getpage.php?name=privacy

skip navigation
About UsExecutive StaffAuxiliaryHistoryMission StatementHospital EventsHospital NewsVolunteersOur LocationsContact UsCommunity Health Needs AssessmentPatient InfoAccepted Health PlansAdvanced DirectiveHealth InformationPatient AccountsPatient Financial AssistancePatient InfoPatient PortalPay Your BillPricing TransparencyPrivacy NoticeVisitor InfoMedical StaffServicesClinical ServicesDiagnostic ServicesHome HealthHospiceIMH CafeteriaNew Leaf CateringOncology ServicesOutpatient ServicesPrompt CareResident HomeSpecialty ClinicSupport ServicesCareersCurrent Job OpeningsEmployee BenefitsPhysician RecruitmentOur Commmunity
Search
Privacy Policy
This Notice describes how medical information about you may be used and disclosed, and how you can get access to this information.
Please review it carefully.
If you have questions about this Notice or our privacy practices, please contact Iroquois Memorial Hospital and Resident Home HIPAA Privacy Officer at 815.432.7743.
At Iroquois Memorial Hospital and Resident Home, we care about your privacy and are committed to protecting and preserving it.
We understand that health information about you is personal and that you may be concerned over how it is used.
The Notice of Privacy Practices describes the limited ways in which Iroquois Memorial Hospital and Resident Home may use and disclose health information about you.
It also describes your rights and our obligations with respect to personal health information.
We promise to comply with the privacy practices described in this Notice, and do our best to treat personal health information about you with the utmost care.
This Notice applies to all use and disclosure of health information about you that is made by health care professionals, staff, employees, students, trainees, volunteers and certain associates of Iroquois Memorial Hospital and Resident Home.
It also applies to any sharing of information among facilities and locations within the Iroquois Memorial Hospital and Resident Home system.
Your personal doctor may have different policies regarding use and disclosure of health information about you.
You should check with each of your personal doctors and obtain a copy of the Notice of Privacy Practices applicable to their respective use and disclosure of health information.
We are required by law and committed as an institution to maintain the privacy of protected health information and to provide individuals with this Notice of our legal duties and privacy practices with respect to protected health information.
We are also required by law to comply with the terms and privacy practices stated in our Notice that is currently in effect, and we pledge to you that we will do so.
Please review this Notice carefully and feel free to contact us about how we use protected health information about you.
This Notice includes the following information:
How we use and disclose information about youSpecial situations regarding information use and disclosureYour right concerning health information about youOther uses and disclosures of information about youChanges to this NoticeComplaintsContact information
IROQUOIS MEMORIAL HOSPITAL AND RESIDENT HOME NOTICE OF PRIVACY PRACTICES
Send Mail
Site Designed & Powered by FastHealth Corporation
Copyright © 2020 FastHealth Corporation
Terms Privacy
